So, what do we think of my Halloween get
up, darlings?
Wow, Rarity, did you make it yourself?
Of course, she made it herself. What is
she supposed to be? A ball sack.
Rainbow Dash, be supportive.
Support these huge nuts. Stained ass is
literally bursting out the back because
it couldn't contain the force of the
massive cheeks.
Can I sit next to you, Rainbow Dash?
No,
you can come sit next to Mir.
Oh, no. That's That's okay. I'll just
stand. Your turn to show off your
costume, Applejack.
Yeah, come on out, you [__] Show this
group of bad [__] so we can judge you
harshly.
Oh, that's it. We all agreed to put on a
costume. What are you doing, [__] This
is my costume and dress is a scare crow.
It looks more like you put on a dirty
ass plaid shirt and called it a day.
You know how it is for me. As a simple
farm girl, I don't make as much as the
rest of y'all. And I can't afford that
spirit Halloween [__] But I still
wanted to feel included because you're
my friends.
Haha. Look, every pony you can see she's
missing one of her front teeth because
hillbillies don't have good dental
hygiene. That's cool, but it also means
you're staying home right
now. Why in Todd Nation do I got to go
home?
During events like Halloween, a girl
group's collective presentation is often
judged by its weakest looking members.
So to maintain aesthetic equilibrium,
all costumes must be of comparable
quality. A cheap ass outfit destabilizes
the group's overall impression. And so
the outlier must be corrected or
removed. Yeah. Are you mentally
challenged? Well, damn [__] If
that's how you're going to be, I'll just
go home then, and y'all won't see me
till morning. Yeah, go do that. Oh, so I
can't go as a scarecrow, but Flutter can
throw on a dirty ass knife gown and put
a plastic tooth on her head. And
suddenly the [__] is the actual tooth
fairy. And Rainbow Dash can put on a
tight black leotard to make her tits and
ass look bigger. Actually, that wasn't
the intended purpose of this costume.
It's not even that tight. My tits and
ass cheeks just always look this big.
But thanks for the compliment. By the
way, that costume makes you look fat,
[__]
Applejack, can you stop critiquing our
costumes? It's really weird.
[__] you don't even got a proper
broomstick. You're holding a swifter
feather duster. which will be up your
ass in 5 seconds if you don't stop being
how you are right now. This is why no
pony likes you and why you are slowly
losing friends by the day and why the
only pony who ever wants to hang out
with you is your sister Sweetie Bell.
You have no idea how happy every pony in
this room right now would be if you went
home and tied a rope around your neck
and then tied the other half to a
ceiling fan and then jumped off a chair.
I thought you all were my friends.
Well, I'm sorry you felt that way.
I'm not. Why does it feel like I'm the
only one who didn't rely on sex appeal
when making my costume?
Oh, we are going to get so much candy
tonight, girls. I can feel it.
Pinkie Pie, can you shut up? Hey,
Twilight, can you go do something about
Celestia? She's been staring in my
window and not saying anything for the
last 45 minutes.
Uh, Twilight Sparkle, you caught me.
Good evening.
Why are you standing at this window?
Well, I can't exactly stand at Rarity's
other one. It's too short for me. This
one is the perfect height to fit my
needs, which is to watch you. Actually,
come up higher, [__] I need to talk to
you face to face. I am hosting a
Halloween party in exactly 1 hour from
now, and I need 300 of Pinkie Pie's
special cookies delivered there before
midnight or Pinkie Pie will suffer grave
consequences. Do you hear me? I'm asking
if you hear me. Respond to me, [__]
[__] Why aren't you speaking? I will
kill you.
Change of plans, Pinkie Pie. The rest of
us are going trick-or-treating, but
you're going to have to head back home
and bake up 300 cookies for Celestia.
Are you girls ready to go?
I know you heard me, Pinkie Pie.
I don't want to do that. I want to hang
out with my girls.
No, do as she says. Pinkie Pie, we kind
of don't like hanging out with you
anyway.
Sup everyone, K5 here. Hope you're
enjoying the video so far. This video
was brought to you by Tron Aliens, which
is alien theaters right now. We're to go
out and buy your tickets after you're
done watching this episode if you want
to watch some good [__]
He oopsies. I made a messy wussy.
Is that you ready? I can't see you
through my tears.
Oh, yes, it's me, darling. How did you
know? Perhaps it was my highly expensive
perfume that I had imported from
Canterlot for a whole $18. What are you
doing here? Shouldn't you be out
gathering yummy candies with our gals?
Oh, Pinky, dear, you know I am a lady of
refinement. The idea of going doortodoor
begging for candy is ludicrous.
So, it has nothing to do with you being
a 40year-old woman who doesn't want to
look weird tagging along with a bunch of
20somes.
Don't get the wrong idea now, Pinky.
It's It's not like I'd be embarrassed to
partake in such events. Age is just a
number after all.
Well, whatever your reason. I got like
300 cookies to bake in 4 hours, so
please leave me be.
Why, that's exactly why I'm here. I
heard your plight, darling. I know if we
work to
Damn [__] Some ponies been eating
some beans. I know if we work together,
we can knock out those cookies in no
time and enjoy the fun festivities with
our gals.
Um, Pinkie Pie, would you prayel tell me
what it is that you are doing with those
extremely sharp shards of glass?
I'm making cookies. The glass makes the
cookies crunchier.
You You don't actually know how to bake,
do you?
Oh, please don't tell anyone. This is
all I have. My whole thing is baking
because I'm a [__] If ponies find out
I don't know how, I'll have nothing
left.
Darling, it's not the end of the world
because we all already think very little
of you because you're [__] as
[__] [__] I'll teach you how to make
proper cookies because I am at least
normal.
Oh, thank you, Rarity. You're such a
good friend. The first thing we need is
flour. Can you go into the back and grab
some?
Oh, sweet Celestia. Pinky. What the hell
is all this?
That's just my supply. I buy them across
the street from Dollar Tree, then put
them up for sale in my shop and resell
them for four times the price.
That's illegal.
Oh, I didn't know that. But it makes me
so much money, so I'm not going to stop.
Why the [__] are there 17 whole ass
empty Oreo boxes in the trash can?
Tola and Star Song, my besties. Oh my
god, those are some spooktasted
costumes.
Like, thanks a ton, [__] I'm dressed
as a world famous pop star.
Haha. Well, the point of Halloween is
indeed to dress up as something you'll
never be.
So, why are you here? Well, let's just
say unfortunately one of us wasn't into
the whole following little cults around
the neighborhood on Halloween night
idea.
Yeah. So, we decided we would like see
what kind of festive goodies you were
selling in your [__] shop tonight.
Then find some lost Colts to suck on.
What?
I said buy some lollipops we can suck
on.
Repeat that first part again.
Pinkie Pie makes the best godamn
cookies. Holy [__]
That's not what you said. Well, you're
just in time to help us bake 3,000 of
them for Princess Celestia's Halloween
bash.
Bake like ew, pinky. You know, we don't
know how to do that. Like, everything we
eat is pre-made because we're rich as
[__]
Come now, girls. We're My Little Ponies.
What even is our purpose for living if
we don't know how to bake sugar cookies?
But just between us fine ladies, our
little pink princess here. I'm afraid
she has a terrible secret and that is
she doesn't know how to bake either.
Rarity, how could you tell them that now
they hate me?
Oh my [__] god, Pinky. Like don't be
like that now. We like don't hate you.
You don't.
We're just like really super
disappointed in your ass because like we
thought you could like do something.
You don't understand Star Song. If I
fail this order, Celestia is going to
kill me. Such as the fate of all who
fail the sun goddess.
She's right.
Then we're not going to let that happen.
Right, girls?
Pinkie Pie, will you come inside
already? We need you to pack up your one
singular cookie and scadaddle. Shut up.
If Salia keeps a wood and kills me, this
can be my last smoke. I want to enjoy
this.
I'm sorry this had to happen, Pinkie
Pie. It's whatever, you pop bastard.
Hey, you want a cigarette? Um, we don't
smoke
then. Get out of my face.
I'm going to kill you, man. I'm going to
kill you.
Why don't you try adding a little less
flour this time?
Don't talk to me in a patronizing way,
Star Song. I know what I am doing.
Well, we gave it our best shot, [__]
but Celestia's Halloween bash starts in
7 minutes. There's no time for another
batch of these sweet little [__]
Oh my god. Like, I literally can't even
anymore. I have to come clean.
You're a cop.
Read the badge.
You've been a secret health inspector
this whole time. Star, how could you?
Pinkie Pie is supposed to be our friend.
She's a what? Get the hell out of my
shop.
Oh my god. Pinky, don't be so dramatic.
Like, I didn't want this. Okay, in my
eyes, you were like the best baker in
the world. I was totally going to give
you like five stars across the board. I
was literally rooting for you.
You were You mean you weren't trying to
get my shop shut down?
And now this is like literally worse for
me than it is for you because I told
every pony that your cookies were like
the best in in the whole [__] world.
And now they're going to find out you've
just been reselling Dollar Tree cookies.
Now every pony is going to know that I
actually love Trashy Offbrand Dollar
Tree cookies. My reputation is going to
be so totally ruined.
Hey girls, check it out.
Don't look at that one. It's hideous.
Pinky, this cookie. It's like perfect.
Are you dead ass? You're really not just
saying that so I don't kill myself.
Darling, it's beautiful. We'll just have
to take this single cookie to Princess
Celestia's Halloween bash and hope it
will be enough to satisfy her greed. No,
I want Twilight and the girls to see it
first. I want those [__] to know
about all the hard work I did. I want
them to gravel at my feet.
If if we want more JL movie, guys, like
we got to support this [__] Like like
even if the movie's bad, like it might
be bad. Like I can't personally say that
cuz it's I'm sponsoring [__] and if I
said it's bad Joe, he would come for my
ass. Like I would I like he would like I
would be taking a dump and [__] and he
would just come running into my house
with like a baseball bat and I would I
would have to stand up butt naked
and say Joe get the get the hell out of
my house and then we would just throw
down like we would be fist fighting and
[__] I'm winning of course because like
no one can beat me. I'm here.
You can't beat me. Why are you attacking
me in my own house with a baseball bat?
Like, are are you stupid? Like, you
can't beat me. If I went to your house
and attacked you with a baseball while
you're taking a [__] a fat dump and [__]
in the safety of your own home, how
would that make you feel, Jaro? I bet
you wouldn't like that, would you? No,
you would not. But I would still kick
your ass because I'm better than you.
I'm a better actor than you will ever
be. So don't you come running up to me
while I'm taking a dump. [__]
I wish you would.
I wish you would try. I wish you would
run up on me while I'm think of [__] so
I could [__] on your face. You are a
[__]
Haha, Pinkie Pie, you are so random.
Pinkie Pie Rarity, you got to check out
how much candy we got.
Shut up, Dyke. I've got something
important to show you. I made a cookie,
girls. Can you guess where I'm hiding
it?
Is it in your stanky ass butt crack
again?
Twilight guessed correctly, which means
she gets to have the first bite.
Where's the other 299?
She only made one, but she did her best,
and that's what matters.
Uh, no. Celestia is going to kill her. I
bet it's not even good. Let me try this
[__]
Yep. Just as I thought. This [__] is
putrid.
Let me try.
Can I have a piece?
[__] there's none left. She just made
a single damn cookie.
Don't worry about what they say, Pinkie
Pie. You did your best and that's what
matters. Oh, Celestia is not going to
like the sound of this.
Rarity, stop telling her that. Only what
Celestia says matters. And Celestia said
she wanted 300 cookies by midnight or
Pinkie Pie will be murdered.
Oh my Celestia. Will Celestia really
kill me? Do you think she will show
mercy?
No, she doesn't really do stuff like
that.
Celestia, I don't think anyone is going
to show up tonight. It's been 2 hours
and the party is going to be over in 30
minutes. Should I start cleaning up?
Nonsense. A half an hour is still plenty
of time for some pony to show up and
dance the night away.
Celestia, don't do this to yourself. Not
again.
You're right, my evil moon sister. Maybe
maybe this was a bad idea after all.
I'll just go to bed and go down to
Ponyville tomorrow and choose which
women or children shall die for this
treachery against me.
Do you want me to heat up some of that
canned meat loaf you like so much?
No thanks. I'll just poop and go to bed.
What do you want, Princess Luna? I'm
pooping.
I'm just checking to see if you're doing
okay,
[__] What the [__] do you think? I
just [__] pooped and there isn't any
[__] toilet paper left. What the [__]
happened to all of the [__] toilet
paper? You [__] You went outside and
threw it all into the trees to make it
look like ghosts were in the tree.
Huh? How look at that, Luna. Doesn't the
toilet paper in the tree look like a
bunch of tiny ghosts?
No, that was a stupid idea anyway. What
if ponies had to go to the bathroom at
some point during the party?
Well, I guess they would have no choice
but to walk around with big poopy butts.
You're right, Luna. It's my fault that I
ended up in this position due to my own
greed and lust. I deserve to go to bed
tonight without wiping my ass.
Whoa, look at that. Does Princess
Celestia know she has toilet paper stuck
in her tree? Maybe we should tell her.
No way. Are you insane? She'll [__]
kill us.
Wait a minute. Pinkie Pie still owes me
3,000 cookies. Pinkie Pie, you have
failed me for the last time. For your
punishment, I shall turn Applejack into
a bag of coffee beans.
What?
Please, no, not Applejack. She's my best
friend. Thank God. I don't really like
Applejack.
Applejack. Applejack, speak to me. She
can speak no longer, Twilight. The life
strings that kept her tethered to this
world have been cut. Your friend is
gone. Her consciousness is now just
beans.
Damn. Well, that's that.
Heat.
Heat up here.